const data = {
  1: {
    question:
      'What behavior of the JavaScript compiler allows us to use functions and variables before they are declared in code?',
    answer: 'hoisting',
  },
  2: {
    question: 'This is a global JavaScript language object provided by the browser',
    answer: 'window',
  },
  3: {
    question: 'The most famous search machine in the world',
    answer: 'google',
  },
  4: {
    question:
      'The method of the Event interface prevents the current event from further spread during the capture and bubbling stages.',
    answer: 'stopPropagation',
  },
  5: {
    question:
      'It\'s a root "abstract" class. Instances of this class can\'t be created. The class is a basis for all events.',
    answer: 'eventTarget',
  },
  6: {
    question: 'Who is attributed with inventing Git?',
    answer: 'Torvalds',
  },
  7: {
    question:
      'Which data structure is typically used for implementing Last-In-First-Out (LIFO) operations?',
    answer: 'stack',
  },
  8: {
    question:
      "It's a module builder that allows you to compile JavaScript modules into a single JS file",
    answer: 'webpack',
  },
  9: {
    question:
      "It's a programming language positioned as a web application development tool that extends the capabilities of JavaScript",
    answer: 'typescript',
  },
  10: {
    question:
      'This corporation owns and developer different hardware such as GitHub, Azure, Visual Studio and etc',
    answer: 'Microsoft',
  },
};

export default data;
